

HIREN PATEL

WEB DEVELOPER + SEO

◆ BRANDON, R7B2M6, CANADA

◆ 2049221305

• DETAILS •

B7-1530B 20th Street
Brandon, R7B2M6
Canada
2049221305
hirenpatel6777@gmail.com

Date of birth 15/03/1992

LINKSLinkedIn

SKILLSHTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap 4

Java Script

jQuery

AJAX

Angular JS

XML

Git

Wordpress

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Social Media Marketing

Google Analytics

Google Search Console

On Page SEO

SEMrush

Screaming Frog

HOBBIES

PROFILE

Over 5+ years experience in IT industry specifically in UI/UX Designer. a Bachelor of Engineering degree in computer science. Top-notch communication and multitasking skills with a proactive mentality and flexible approach to problem solving. Goal-oriented and proficient team player motivated to increase abilities and make a positive impact on team projects.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Developer + SEO at PBC Multi Media, Brandon, MB, Canada

December 2020 — Present

- · Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients.
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times.
- Remained knowledgeable in new standards, technologies, and trends in website development.
- Incorporating functionalities and features into websites.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- Designing visual imagery for websites and ensuring that they are in line with branding for clients.
- Effetively multitasked and worked well with internal and external teams.

Web Designer at Sanah Infosolutions Pvt.Ltd., Vadodara, India

August 2017 — February 2020

- Remained dedicated to emerging technology and the latest digital marketing concepts.
- · Created detaisl technical and user documentation.
- Designing sample pages including colors and fonts.
- Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure.
- Testing and improving the design of the website.
- Establishing design guidelines, standards, and best practices.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards

Web Designer at PriyaSharm Software Pvt. Ltd., Vadodara, India

August 2016 — August 2017

- · Testing and improving the design of the website.
- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- · Email blast design using photo shop.

Web Designer at LenDen Club(Innofin Solutions Private Limited), Mumbai, India.

July 2015 — July 2016

- Maintaining the appearance of websites by enforcing content standards.
- Testing and improving the design of the website.

EDUCATION

• LANGUAGES •
English
Hindi
Gujarati

Music Travelling

Reading

Bachelor of engineering (Computer Science), R.R Institution Of Technology (VTU), Bangalore- India

August 2009 — May 2013

Soft Skills

Team player, Self-learner, Advanced problem-solver, Innovative, Creative, Good Communication

Operating Systems

Windows 11/10/8/7/XP, Linux, Mac OS

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Volunteering

- Active Member Of BAPS Youth Club.
- Leader in Ozone event Organized by RRIT college.

■ REFERENCES

• References available upon request